Academic Affairs and Provost, Office of Senior V.P. for; Records ua500
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Program Registration Letters, 1964-2023; 3; 0.67 cubic ft.
  - Various Graduate Programs - Discontinuance, 1996 September 27 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 22)
    Discontinuation of the following degrees: Business Education, M.S.; Business and Distributive Education, M.S.; Educational Communications, M.S., Advanced Certificate; English 7-12, M.S.; German 7-12, M.S.; Russian 7-12, M.S.; Spanish 7-12, M.S.
  - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1967 April 5 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 23)
    Includes the following degrees: Art, B.A.; Economics, B.A.; English, B.A., Ph.D.; French, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Geography, B.A.; German, B.A., M.A.; History, B.A., M.A., M.S., Ph.D.; Inter-American Language and Area Studies, B.A.; Latin, B.A., M.A.; Mathematics, B.A., B.S., M.A., M.S.; Music, B.A.; Philosophy, B.A., M.A.; Political Science, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Psychology, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Russian, B.A., M.A.; Sociology, B.A., M.A.; Spanish, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Speech and Dramatic Art, B.A.; Accounting, B.S.; Astronomy and Space Science, B.S., M.S.; Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.A., M.S.; Biology, B.S., M.A., M.S., Ph.D.; Business Administration, B.S., M.B.A.; Chemistry, B.S., M.A., M.S., Ph.D.; Geology, B.S., Geology, M.S.; Physics, B.S., M.A., M.S., Ph.D.; Science, B.S.; Science-Medical Technology, B.S.; Comparative Literature, M.A.; Dramatic Art, M.A.; English Literature, M.A., M.S.; Political Economy, M.A., Ph.D.; Public Affairs, M.A., Ph.D.; Earth Science, M.S.; Speech, Speech Correction, and Audiology, M.S.; Librarianship (College, Government, Public, Serial), M.L.S.; Administrative Management, M.P.A.; Human Resources, M.P.A.; International Affairs, M.P.A.; Public Finance, M.P.A.; Public Information, M.P.A.; Urban Development, M.P.A.; Public Administration, D.P.A.; Social Welfare, M.S.W.
    - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1967 April 5
    - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1967 April 5
  - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1969 March 5 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 24)
    Includes the following degrees: American Studies, B.A.; Anthropology, B.A.; Art, B.A.; Art (Studio, M.A.); Biology, B.A., B.S., M.S., Ph.D.; Economics, B.A., B.S., M.A.; English, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; French, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Geography, B.A.; German, B.A., M.A.; Greek, B.A.; History, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Inter-American Language and Area Studies, B.A.; Italian, B.A.; Latin, B.A.; Mathematics, B.A., B.S., M.A., Ph.D.; Music, B.A.; Philosophy, B.A., M.A.; Political Science, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Pschology, B.A., M.A., Ph.D.; Russian, B.A., M.A.; Sociology, B.A., M.A.; Spanish, B.A., M.A.; Speech and Dramatic Art, B.A.; Accounting, B.S.; Astronomy and Space Science, B.S., M.S., Ph.D.; Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., Ph.D.; Business Administration, B.S., M.B.A.; Chemistry, B.S., M.S., Ph.D.; Geology, B.S., M.S.; Physics, B.S., M.S., Ph.D.; Science, B.S.; Science-Medical Technology, B.S.; Art History, M.A.; Comparative Literature, M.A.; Criminal Justice, M.A., Ph.D.; Dramatic Art, M.A.; Latin-American Studies, M.A.; Political Economy, M.A., Ph.D.; Public Affairs, M.A.; Social Studies, M.A.; Business, M.S.; Computer Science, M.S.; Speech Correction and Audiology, M.S.; Librarianship (Public, College, Special), M.L.S.; Administrative Management, M.P.A.; Human Resources, M.P.A.; International Affairs, M.P.A.; Public Finance, M.P.A.; Public Information, M.P.A.; Quantitative Analysis for Decision-making, M.P.A.; Urban Development, M.P.A.; Social Welfare, M.P.A.; Classics, Ph.D.; Educational Foundations, Ph.D.; Romance Languages, Ph.D.; Public Administration, D.P.A.
    - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1969 March 5
    - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1969 March 5
  - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs, 1970 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 25)
    Includes the following degrees: School Administrator-Supervisor, Ed.D., Certificate; School District Administrator, Ed.D., Certificate; Elementary Teacher (N-6), M.S.; Elementary Teacher (N-9), M.S.; Speech and Hearing Handicapped, B.A., B.S., M.A., M.S.; Italian 7-12, B.A.; Secondary Academic Subjects, 7-12 (English, Social Studies, Mathematics, French, German, Latin, Russian, Spanish, Biology, Chemistry, Physics, Earth Science), B.A., M.A., B.S., M.S.; Commerce, B.S., M.S.; Commerce and Distributive Occupation Subjects, B.S., M.S.; Library, M.L.S.; Speech, B.A., B.S., M.A., M.S.; Guidance, M.A., M.S., Ed.D.; School Psychologist, Certificate.
  - Various Graduate and Undergraduate Programs for the Training of Veterans, 1970-1971 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 26)
    Public Accounting, B.S.; Business Administration, B.S., M.B.A.; Accounting, M.S.; Secondary School Teaching Sequence, M.S.; Criminal Justice, M.A., Ph.D.; Politicl Science, M.A., Ph.D.; Political Economy, M.A., Ph.D.; Public Affairs, M.A.; Public Administration, M.P.A., D.P.A.; Library Science, M.L.S.; Social Welfare, M.S.W.
  - Various Teacher Education Programs, 1964 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 27)
    Includes: Teachers of speech and hearing handicapped, English, Social Studies, Mathematics, Foreign Language, Biology, Chemistry, Physics, B.A., B.S., M.A., M.S.; Teachers of earth science, speech, B.A., B.S.
  - Various Unidentified Programs, 1981 April 7 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 28)
  - Women and Public Policy, Certificate, 1987 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 29)
  - Women's Studies, B.A., 1989 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 30)
  - Women's Studies, M.A., 1999 (Box 3 (3-Program Registration Letters), Folder 31)
  - Actuarial Mathematical Sciences, B.S., 2023
    - Actuarial Mathematical Sciences, B.S., 2023
    - Actuarial Mathematical Sciences, B.S., 2023
    - Actuarial Mathematical Sciences, B.S., 2023
  - Africana Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Africana Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Africana Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Africana Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
  - Anthropology, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Anthropology, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Anthropology, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Anthropology, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
  - Art History, B.A., 2022
  - Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Atmospheric Science, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
  - Biology, B.A. M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Biology, B.A. M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Biology, B.A. M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Biology, B.A. M.S., J.D., 2023
  - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
    - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
    - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
    - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
    - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
    - Biology, B.S., M.S., J.D., O.D., 2022
  - Business Administration, B.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Business Administration, B.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Business Administration, B.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Business Administration, B.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
  - Chemistry, B.A., M.S., 2023
    - Chemistry, B.A., M.S., 2023
    - Chemistry, B.A., M.S., 2023
    - Chemistry, B.A., M.S., 2023
  - Chemistry, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Chemistry, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Chemistry, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Chemistry, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - Chemistry, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2022
  - Communications, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Communications, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Communications, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - Communications, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
  - Computer Science, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Computer Science, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Computer Science, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Computer Science, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
  - Cybersecurity, B.S., 2022
    - Cybersecurity, B.S., 2022
    - Cybersecurity, B.S., 2022
  - Economics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2023
    - Economics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2023
    - Economics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2023
    - Economics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2023
    - Economics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2023
  - Quantitative Economics and Data Analytics, B.S., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., J.D., M.A., 2023
  - Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security, and Cybersecurity, B.A., 2022
  - Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security, and Cybersecurity, B.S., 2022
  - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2022
  - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - English, B.A., M.A., M.S., J.D., 2023
  - Geography, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Geography, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Geography, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Geography, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Geography, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S., 2023
  - History, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - History, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - History, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - History, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
    - History, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2022
  - Human Biology, B.S., 2023
  - Human Development, B.S., 2022
  - Informatics, B.S., 2021
  - Journalism, B.A., 2022
  - Latin America, Carribbean, and U.S. Latino Studies, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Latin America, Carribbean, and U.S. Latino Studies, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Latin America, Carribbean, and U.S. Latino Studies, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Latin America, Carribbean, and U.S. Latino Studies, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
  - Linguistics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Linguistics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Linguistics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Linguistics, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
  - Mathematics, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2023
  - Mathematics, B.S., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.S., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.S., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.S., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Mathematics, B.S., M.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
  - Music, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Music, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Music, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
    - Music, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., 2022
  - Nanoscale Engineering,and Nanobioscience, B.S., M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Engineering,and Nanobioscience, B.S., M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Engineering,and Nanobioscience, B.S., M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Engineering,and Nanobioscience, B.S., M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
  - Nanoscale Science and Nanobioscience, B.S. M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Science and Nanobioscience, B.S. M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Science and Nanobioscience, B.S. M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
    - Nanoscale Science and Nanobioscience, B.S. M.S., Ph.D., M.D./Ph.D., 2023
  - Nursing, B.S. R.N., M.S., 2023
  - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
  - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
    - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
    - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
    - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
    - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
    - Political Science, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.P.A., 2022
  - Psychology, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.S., 2023
    - Psychology, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.S., 2023
    - Psychology, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.S., 2023
    - Psychology, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.S., 2023
    - Psychology, B.A., J.D., M.A., M.S.I.S., M.S., 2023
  - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
    - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
    - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
    - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
    - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
    - Public Policy and Administration, B.A., M.S.I.S., J.D., M.P.A., 2021
  - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Sociology, B.A., M.A., J.D., M.P.A., M.S.I.S., 2022
  - Theatre, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Theatre, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Theatre, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Theatre, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
    - Theatre, B.A., J.D., M.S.I.S., 2022
  - Urban Studies and Planning, B.A., 2023
  - Women's Gender and Sexuality Studies, B.A., M.A., 2023
    - Women's Gender and Sexuality Studies, B.A., M.A., 2023
    - Women's Gender and Sexuality Studies, B.A., M.A., 2023
  - B.S. in Computer Engineering, 2014
    - B.S. in Computer Engineering, 2014
    - B.S. in Computer Engineering, 2014
    - B.S. in Computer Engineering, 2014
  - B.S. in Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, 2014
    - B.S. in Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, 2014
    - B.S. in Computer Science and Applied Mathematics, 2014
  - B.S. in Human Development, 2014
  - Reactivation of Theater leading to B.A., 2014
  - B.A. in Urban Studies and Planning, 2014
  - B.A. in Women's Studies Title Change, 2014
  - Advanced Certificate in International Health and Human Rights, 2015
  - B.A. and J.D. in African Studies, 2015
  - B.A. in Emergency Prepardness, Homeland Security and Cybersecurity, 2015
  - B.A. in Public Policy, 2015
  - Advanced Certificate in Computing Education, 2016
  - M.S.and Ph.D. in Educational Policy and Leadership, 2016
  - B.A. in English and M.A. in Liberal Studies, 2016
  - M.S. in Higher Education, 2016
  - C.A.S. and Ph.D. in Literacy, 2016
    - C.A.S. and Ph.D. in Literacy, 2016
    - C.A.S. and Ph.D. in Literacy, 2016
  - B.A./M.S. in Mental Health Counseling, 2016
  - Latin America, Carribbean, and U.S. Latino Studies program name change, 2016
  - Advanced Graduate Certificate in Community College Leadership, 2017
  - M.S. Program in Counseling Psychology, 2017
  - Ph.D. in Counseling Psychology, 2017
  - M. S in Data Science, 2017
  - M.S. in Geographic Information Science, 2017
  - Graduate Certificate Program in International Education Management, 2017
  - Graduate Certificate in Teaching English to Speakers of Other Languages, 2017
  - B.A. in Rhetoric and Communications, 2017
  - Ph.D. in Curriculum and Instruction, 2018
  - M.S. and Ph.D. in Electrical and Computer Engineering, 2018
  - M.S. in Information Science (2 concentration tracks), 2018
  - M.S. in Information Science Library, 2018
  - M.A. in International Education Management and Leadership, 2018
  - M.S. in Professional Accountancy, 2018
  - B.S. in Computer Engineering, 2018
  - B.S. in Human Development with concentration in Higher Education, 2018
  - B.A. in Political Science, 2018
  - B.A. in Public Policy and Management, 2018
  - B.S. Math and M.S. Data Science 2019
  - History, M.A., 2008
  - Pilot Graduate Level Clinically Rich Teacher Preparation Program (GLCRTPPP), Adolescence: Special Education Generalist, M.S., 2011
  - Advanced Certificate program in Online Learning and Teaching, 2011
  - Economics Curriculum, B.S., M.A., 2011
  - Economics, B.S., M.A., 2011
  - Early Childhood/Childhood Education, M.S., 2014
  - Advanced Certificate in Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security and Cyber Security, 2015
  - Advanced Certificate Program in Global Health Services, 2014
  - Advanced Graduate Certificate Program in Information Security, 2011
  - Master of International Affairs, 2015
  - Nanoscale Engineering and Nanoscale Science, B.S., M.S., 2014
  - Advanced Certificate program in Professional Science Management, 2010
  - Advanced Certificate in English Studies, 2015
  - Advanced Certificate in Teaching Composition, 2015
  - Advanced Certificate in Adolescent Special Education for Childhood Special Education, 2015
  - Advanced Certificate in Adolescent Special Education for Content Teachers, 2015
  - Adolescent Education, B.S., 2024
    - Adolescent Education, B.S., 2024
    - Adolescent Education, B.S., 2024
  - Chinese Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Chinese Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Chinese Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
    - Chinese Studies, B.A., J.D., M.S., 2023
  - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.S., M.A., J.D., 2023
    - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.S., M.A., J.D., 2023
    - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.S., M.A., J.D., 2023
    - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.S., M.A., J.D., 2023
    - Criminal Justice, B.A., M.S., M.A., J.D., 2023
  - Emergency Preparedness, Homeland Security and Cybersecurity, B.A., 2023
  - Early Childhood and Childhood Education, B.S., 2024
  - East Asian Studies, B.A., 2023
  - Japanese Studies, B.A., 2023
  - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Physics, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
  - Social Welfare, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Social Welfare, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
    - Social Welfare, B.S., M.S., J.D., 2023
  - Spanish, B.A., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Spanish, B.A., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Spanish, B.A., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Spanish, B.A., M.A., M.S., 2023
    - Spanish, B.A., M.A., M.S., 2023
  - Graduate Certificate in Africana Studies, 2024
  - Art, B.S., 2024
  - Emergency Management and Homeland Security, M.S., 2024
  - Accounting, B.S., 2024
    - Accounting, B.S., 2024
    - Accounting, B.S., 2024
    - Accounting, B.S., 2024
  - Biomedical Sciences, M.S., 2024
    - Biomedical Sciences, M.S., 2024
    - Biomedical Sciences, M.S., 2024
  - Interdisciplinary, Biochemistry & Molecular Chemistry, Enviromental Science, or Financial Market Regulation, B.S., 2024
    - Interdisciplinary, Biochemistry & Molecular Chemistry, Enviromental Science, or Financial Market Regulation, B.S., 2024
    - Interdisciplinary, Biochemistry & Molecular Chemistry, Enviromental Science, or Financial Market Regulation, B.S., 2024
- Program Accreditation Letters, 1957-2000; 1970-2000; 4; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by accrediting body.
  This series consists of letters from external accreditation organizations confirming the accreditation status of academic programs.
  - Accreditation Council for Graduate Medical Education - Preventive Medicine/Public Health, Residency, 1990 November 27 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 1)
  - American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business, 1980 December (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 2)
  - American Chemical Society - Chemistry, 1983 May 16 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 3)
  - American Library Association - Department of Librarianship, 1957 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 4)
  - American Library Association - Master of Library Science, 1983 June 28 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 5)
  - American Library Association - Master of Library Science, 1990 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 6)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1980 December 31 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 7)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1983 November 15 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 8)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1985 December 3 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 9)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1987 November 2 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 10)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1989 September 20 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 11)
  - American Psychological Association - Clinical Psychology, Ph.D., 1999 July 28 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 12)
  - American Psychological Association - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1980 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 13)
  - American Psychological Association - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1983 August 8 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 14)
  - American Psychological Association - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1988 August 24 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 15)
  - American Psychological Association - Counseling Psychology, Ph.D., 1993 August 30 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 16)
  - American Psychological Association - School Psychology, Psy.D., 1993 August 18 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 17)
  - Computer Science Accreditation Board - Computer Science, 1987 July 29 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 18)
  - Council on Rehabilitation Education - Rehabilitation Counselor Education Program, 1987 August 15 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 19)
  - Council on Rehabilitation Education - Rehabilitation Counselor Education Program, 1991 July 17 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 20)
  - Council on Social Work Education - School of Social Welfare, 1969 June 20 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 21)
  - Council on Social Work Education - School of Social Welfare, 1976 February 17 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 22)
  - Council on Social Work Education - Social Work, B.S., M.S.W., 1988 June 22 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 23)
  - Middle States Commission on Higher Education, 1986 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 24)
  - Middle States Commission on Higher Education, 2000 June 30 (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 25)
  - National Association of Schools of Public Affairs and Administration (NASPAA) - Master of Public Administration, 1988 June (Box 1 (4-Program Accreditation Letters), Folder 26)
- Articulation and Joint Agreements, 1988-2018; 5; 0.17 cubic ft.
  Folders are arranged alphabetically by institution.
  This series consists of articulation agreements and memoranda of understanding between the University at Albany and other institutions. These documents detail joint degree programs, credit transfer agreements, and collaborative research agreements.
  - Clarkson University - 3/2 Engineering Program, Undated (Box 1 (5-Articulation Agreements), Folder 1)
  - National Oceanic and Atmospheric Administration - Memorandum of Agreement, 1999 (Box 1 (5-Articulation Agreements), Folder 2)
  - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute - Engineering Agreement, Undated (Box 1 (5-Articulation Agreements), Folder 3)
  - SUNY Binghamton - 3/2 Engineering Agreement, 1988 (Box 1 (5-Articulation Agreements), Folder 4)
  - University of Natal, South Africa - Memorandum of Understanding, 1996 (Box 1 (5-Articulation Agreements), Folder 5)
  - Community College Transfer Articulation Agreements, 2018 October 18
  - Existing Transfer Articulation Agreements with Programs, 2018
  - Existing Transfer Articulation Agreements with community colleges, 2018
  - Affiliation Agreement with Albany Law School, 2015